<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[delorme]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[delorme]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/delorme/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 11:03:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/delorme/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Campaign Not Hitting the Mark? Blame the Chaos Theory]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever wondered why that seemingly perfect campaign drove very little traffic? Perhaps you saw lots of interactions, but few applications with no obvious reason? Maybe your campaigns generally feel unpredictable? I guess you have asked yourself, “What’s going on?” The answer is simple: Chaos. But what does ‘chaos’ actually mean? Merriam-Webster defines the Chaos Theory as, “a branch of mathematical and physical theory that deals with the nature and consequences of chaos and chaotic systems.” That may be true, but I like to think of it as the slightly catchier ‘Science of Surprises’; the cause of unpredictability. Butterflies and Balloons You’ve heard of The Butterfly Effect, where something as minute as a butterfly fluttering its wings at a particular moment in time can eventually lead to a hurricane several weeks later, right? Well, Chaos Theory is the idea that small actions can have the potential for huge consequences later on. Imagine releasing a bunch of helium balloons together. They float high up into the air, over the roofs of houses, getting smaller and smaller – until they start to lose their helium and head back towards earth. But where will they land? It doesn’t take a genius to work out they won’t land all in the same place. The same philosophy applies to your potential applicants. To start with, and for whatever reason, they all land on the same place on your careers site. Yes! You’ve got them! That’s great, right? Not necessarily. Digital Strategist (Metrics & Campaign Management) Patrick Welch, revealed that based on three million page views, over a six-month period, forty-four per cent of potential applicants who visited a global technology’s career site left after just one visit and without taking any action. It could be the initial look, or complexity of the site. There are a host of reasons why. So what about the remainder who do stay? Well, their pathways will all be slightly different. Chaotic Route Candidates will all differ in the way they search. What they are each looking for will mean they will each follow their own individual paths and create their own pathways. The situation is similar with your job advertisements. Your potential applicants could start by seeing your ad on a job board, but they will all react in different ways. Some could leave without even clicking on your ad. (But you’d find their reasons for leaving would be very different.) Some could click on the ad but the destination site could put them off. But then some (you would hope!) could click through and apply straight away. It’s easy to see how quickly their paths can change. By recognising that every person, and indeed the world we live in, is chaotic, you can gain a whole new insight. A pilot can steer a hot air balloon to a desired location by better understanding the complex dynamics of the atmosphere. But without this knowledge, he has only educated guessing and optimism to help him land successfully. The less knowledge he has, the harder it is to steer the balloon and the more chaotic the flight path becomes. Now, imagine each of your potential applicants is a balloon. By better understanding them, for example, what content is of most interest, what type of ad best suits, the reasons they apply or don’t apply, how they interact with our campaigns and so on, you too can help better steer them through to the process, so they are confident and excited to apply. The Takeaway One detail that may seem small in the grand scheme of things could prevent a person from applying for a role. By our very nature, human beings are complex and chaotic. It’s vital you understand as much as you can about your potential applicants when planning all aspects of a campaign. That way, you can pilot your candidates and make sure they not only land on your careers site safely, but do exactly what you want them to do when they get there as well.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/delorme/campaign-not-hitting-the-mark-blame-the-chaos-theory/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6c3ddbe7-d398-43b7-b9eb-dd1eff03f070</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 11:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Authentic, Aligned, Autonomous - Employer Branding in the Post Control Era]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The pace of change is so fast these days that what we know to be true today, will be challenged tomorrow. Whether at an individual level, in how we see and interact with the world, at corporate level in how our businesses respond to change, or even at societal level; change has never seemed so present. As a British citizen, who spends a great deal of time travelling in Europe, I am reminded almost every week, as I pass through a passport control, that even my identity as a European citizen is on borrowed time. In an era where we recognise our businesses are operating in a state of constant transformation, it is becoming counterintuitive to arrive at a fixed point when it comes to Employer Branding. Meanwhile rigid guidelines become impossible to effectively police in the era of democratic self publishing. Dynamic brands aligned to progressive corporate cultures that hold overall corporate purpose at their heart are where we are headed. What does dynamic branding mean in an employer brand context? From where I sit (currently mid air between London and Munich) enabling a dynamic employer brand means harnessing the power of more of our people to tell our story. We know potential hires want to hear from people, not corporations and we also know the huge value of great content across multiple channels from an inbound marketing perspective. There are three keys to making this work: Authenticity: Content is authentic to the organisation’s culture and to the individual producing it. Alignment: Content is aligned to the audience and with the corporate purpose and vision whilst allowing for tonal variety that reflects the diversity that exists in any organisation. Autonomy: Authors are empowered and enabled to produce content in an autonomous capacity. The work of getting to clarity on the EVP at corporate level remains hugely important in achieving the insight that will enable all this. Our challenge lies in how we drive employer brand activation. In the past we have thought in terms of guidelines. In the future we will think in terms of empowerment and enablement.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/delorme/authentic-aligned-autonomous-employer-branding-in-the-po/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9ad34ea9-2b55-48c3-83fd-5ab60be8d16c</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 11:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>